<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>He Will Carry You</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v6</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Do you ever find yourself asking God where he's been?
Ever get up out of bed saying I can't do this again?
Have you ever been afraid of what tomorrow's gonna to bring?
And you're facing it alone, at least that's what you think</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>I can tell you after going through that valley
Even though I didn't see it at the time
It was in my weakest moments that he held me and I know you'll find</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>He will carry you when you can't go on
He will be your strength when your strength is gone
He will lift you up, he will be enough to get you through
When the road is long and you wanna quit
'Cause you think you've got nothin' left to give
You can fall apart fall into His arms
He will carry you</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>When you get the kind of news that you hoped you'd never hear
When you're chasin' down a dream just to watch it disappear
When somebody that you love turns and walks away
And they leave you standing there with shattered faith</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>You don't have to pick up all the broken pieces
You don't have to try to cover up the scars
You are loved and you can always run to Jesus
Just as you are</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>He will carry you when you can't go on
He will be your strength when your strength is gone
He will lift you up he will be enough to get you through
When the road is long and you wanna quit
'Cause you think you've got nothin' left to give
You can fall apart fall into His arms
He will carry you</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>His heart is never weary, no! He's never tired
Through the toughest fight, through the longest night
Through the flood and through the fire</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
