<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Healing in His Name</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v2 v4 v2 v5 v2 v6 v2 v7 v2</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>He was pierced and wounded, for all of our wrongs
Carried our sorrows, although to us they ever belonged
Through His sacrifice, our souls He has reclaimed
By His wounds, we're mended and forever unashamed</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Healing in His name, oh, there's healing in His name,
By the stripes of Jesus, every sickness overcame,
Come and find the solace where His mercy reigns,
Oh, there's healing, sweet healing, in His holy name.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>He forgives all our sins and heals all disease
Redeems our life from the pit, brings our spirit ease
Crowned with compassion, He renews our days
In His love, there's healing in so many ways</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>The Lord sustains the weary, lifts them from despair
With His mighty power, He answers every prayer
A balm for every heartache, a cure for every pain
His healing flows like rivers, through every vein</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>He sent His word to heal, to save from the grave
In every storm season, He's the One who saves
He calms the troubled waters, speaks peace to our soul
By His hand, we're guided, in His presence, made whole.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Faith makes us whole, like the woman long ago
Touched the hem of His garment, felt His power flow
If we believe, He'll do just the same,
There's healing for the asking in Jesus' mighty name….</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>In that land of glory, where tears shall never flow
Every pain and sorrow, forever laid low
In the presence of Jesus, where the saints abide
We'll find eternal healing, by the Saviors side.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
