<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>In Everything, Give Him Thanks</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>In everything give Him thanks, give Him thanks
In everything give Him thanks, give Him thanks</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>In the good times praise His Name
In the bad times do the same
In everything give the King of Kings all the thanks.
In the good times praise His name
In the bad times do the same
In everything give the King of Kings all the thanks</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>With all of the good things that came his way
It's no wonder you could hear Job say
&quot;The Lord giveth and He taketh away, so I'll still give Him thanks&quot;
But when the tables were all turned around
And all of Job's wealth came crashing down
Job's faith in God had taught him to say &quot;I'll still give Him thanks&quot;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>In the good times I'll praise His name
In the bad times I'll do the same
In everything I'll give the King of Kings all the thanks</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>And in those dark hours when there's no one around
And Satan tries to tell you that God has let you down
In every dark hour the best thing I have found
Is to give God the thanks</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>For He has never, He has never failed me yet
So why should I start now to worry or fret
In everything, in everything I won't ever forget to give God the thanks</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>In everything give Him thanks, give Him thanks.
In everything give Him thanks. we've got to give Him thanks
In the good times praise His Name
In the bad times, church do the same
In everything give the King of Kings all the thanks</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>In my trials, and in my test
When I've tried and I know I've done my best
In everything I'll give the King of Kings all the thanks</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
