<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Led Out Of Bondage</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>God promised to lead His children out of bondage
He said He'd free them from Pharaoh's evil hand
He said He'd guide and protect them on their journey
And lead them to the promised land.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>God's children were slaves in Egypt land
So God took Moses by the hand
He said Moses tell old Pharaoh to set'em free
But Moses wanted a way to get out
Cause in his mind he's beginning to doubt
He said Lord old Pharaoh he ain't a gonna listen to me.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Now the Lord said son throw down that rod
Old Moses did and he cried to God
Cause it turned to a snake as evil and wicked as sin
Then he cried again with an awful wail
The Lord said seize him by the tail
Old Moses did and it turned to a rod again.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>God promised to lead His children out of bondage
He said He'd free them from Pharaoh's evil hand
He said He'd guide and protect them on their journey
And lead them to the promised land.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Well the Lord said Moses I've got power
An I'll be with you every hour
Said go tell Pharaoh to set my children free
Well Moses did but the Lord helped out
He sent a plague to the land about
So old Pharaoh told him to go and let him be.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Well they started out with a cloud that day
And a fire by night to lead the way
But old Pharaoh suddenly decided to change his mind
So he gathered together his soldier band
Got all them chariots throughout the land
Said I'll let them Israelites go some other time.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>God promised to lead His children out of bondage
He said He'd free them from Pharaoh's evil hand
He said He'd guide and protect them on their journey
And lead them to the promised land.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Well they came to the banks of the old Red Sea
Turned to Moses and started to plea
And Moses fell on his knees an there is the sand
The Lord told Moses trust in God
All ya gotta do is just raise that rod
And over these mighty waters stretch your hand.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>Well Moses followed the Lord's command
The waters parted and there is the sand
They saw a path that led to the other shore
Well the ground was dry and they walked on through
And old Pharaoh's army thought they would to
But the waters fell ain't never been seen no more.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>God promised to lead His children out of bondage
He said He'd free them from Pharaoh's evil hand
He said He'd guide and protect them on their journey
And lead them to the promised land.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
