<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>My God is Awesome</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8 v9 v10 v11 v12 v13 v14 v15 v16 v17 v18 v19 v20 v21</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Somebody lift our hands
As we celebrate the greatness of our god
He is great and he is greatly to be praised
This is the worship song that says this, &quot;our God is awesome&quot;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>He can move mountains
(He can move mountains) keep me in the valley
(Keep me in the valley) hide me from the rain
(Hide me from the rain)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Come on, our God is awesome
He heals me when I'm broken
(Heals me when I'm broken)
Gives strength where I've been weakened (strength where I've been weakened)
Forever He will reign (forever He will reign)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Come on, say &quot;my God is awesome&quot;
He can move mountains
(He can move mountains) keep me in the valley
(Keep me in the valley) hide me from the rain
(Hide me from the rain)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>My God is awesome
He heals me when I'm broken
(Heals me when I'm broken)
Strength where I've been weakened (strength where I've been weakened)
Forever He will reign (forever He will reign)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Come on, if you believe it, lift your voice and say
Come on, if you know he's awesome, say it
(Awesome) come on and lift your voice
(Awesome) awesome
(Awesome)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>My God (my God is awesome) come on and testify, awesome
(Awesome) if you believe it, say it
(Awesome) come on and say it
(Awesome) My God</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Think about it, saviour of the whole world
(Savior of the whole world)
Giver of salvation (giver of salvation)
By His stripes (by his stripes I am healed)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>My God is awesome (my God is awesome)
Today I am forgiven (today I am forgiven)
His grace is why I'm living (His grace is why I'm living)
Somebody oughta praise His holy name (praise His holy name)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>Come on and testify, you know He's awesome, say it
come on and lift your voice and say
(Awesome)
(Awesome) come on and say awesome
(Awesome)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>My God (my God is awesome) come on and say awesome
(Awesome) come on, if you believe it, lift your voice
(Awesome)
(Awesome) come on, somebody say.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>He's mighty (He's mighty)
He's mighty (He's mighty)
He's mighty (He's mighty)
He's mighty (He's mighty)
Awesome (awesome)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v13">
      <lines>Come on and lift your voice and testify
Come on and say He's holy (He's holy)
He's holy (He's holy)
He's holy (He's holy)
He's holy (He's holy)
Awesome (awesome)
Come on and lift your voice and say (awesome)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v14">
      <lines>Come on and say, He's great (He's great)
He's great (He's great)
He's great (He's great)
He's great (He's great).
Awesome (awesome) hallelujah, come on and say (awesome)…</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v15">
      <lines>Come on and say, He's mighty (He's mighty)
He's mighty (He's mighty)
He's mighty (He's mighty)
He's mighty (He's mighty)
Awesome (awesome).</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v16">
      <lines>Everybody say awesome (Awesome)
Come on and say, deliverer (deliverer)
Deliverer (deliverer)
Deliverer (deliverer)
Deliverer (deliverer) come on and say (awesome)
Come on and lift your voice if you believe and say (awesome)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v17">
      <lines>Come on and say, He's holy (He's holy)
He's holy (He's holy)
He's holy (He's holy)
He's holy (He's holy)…</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v18">
      <lines>Awesome (awesome)
Come on, everybody oughta testify (awesome)
Somebody lift your voice and say, provider (provider)
Provider (provider)
Provider (provider)
Provider (provider)
Awesome (awesome)…</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v19">
      <lines>Hallelujah, lift your voice (awesome)
Somebody let Hell know, protector (protector)
Protector (protector)
Has He looked out for you? (protector)
Protector (protector) awesome (awesome)
Everybody say, awesome (awesome) let's get outta here.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v20">
      <lines>My God (my God is awesome) He can move mountains
(He can move mountains) keep you in the valley
(Keep me in the valley) hide me from the rain
(Hide me from the rain)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v21">
      <lines>My God is awesome (my God is awesome)
Heals me when I'm broken (heals me when I'm broken)
Strength when I've been weakened (strength where I've been weakened)
Praise His holy name (praise His holy name)
Somebody oughta celebrate the awesome God
Oh, oh, He's awesome</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
