<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Right Attitude</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8 v9 v10 v11 v12 v13 v14 v15</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>I've been on the Mountain with Jesus
And I've been in the Valley so low,
But never one time has He failed me
Unto him with my troubles I go</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>So let me walk with you Jesus
Don't ever leave me alone
For without you I would never,
I would never make heaven my home</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>He found me when I was so lonely
He found me when I was so blue
He found me when no one could help me
When no one knew just what to do.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>So let me walk with you Jesus
Don't ever leave me alone
For without you I would never,
I would never make heaven my home.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Num. 11
[1] And when the people complained,
it displeased the LORD: and the LORD
heard it; and his anger was kindled; and
the fire of the LORD burnt among them,
and consumed them that were in the
uttermost parts of the camp.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Num. 11
[2] And the people cried unto Moses;
and when Moses prayed unto the LORD,
the fire was quenched.
[3] And he called the name of the place
Taberah: because the fire of the LORD
burnt among them.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Num. 11
[4] And the mixt multitude that was among
them fell a lusting: and the children of Israel
also wept again, and said, Who shall give
us flesh to eat?
[5] We remember the fish, which we did
eat in Egypt freely; the cucumbers, and
the melons, and the leeks, and the onions,
and the garlick:</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Num. 11
[6] But our soul is dried away: there is nothing
at all, beside this manna, before our eyes.
[7] And the manna was as coriander seed, &amp;
the colour thereof as the colour of bdellium.
[8] And the people went about, and gathered it,
&amp; ground it in mills, or beat it in a mortar, &amp; baked
it in pans, and made cakes of it: and the taste of it
was as the taste of fresh oil.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>Num. 11
[9] And when the dew fell upon the camp
in the night, the manna fell upon it.
[10] Then Moses heard the people weep
throughout their families, every man in the
door of his tent: &amp; the anger of the LORD
was kindled greatly; Moses also was
displeased.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>Amos 8
11 Behold, the days come, saith the
Lord God, that I will send a famine in
the land, not a famine of bread, nor
a thirst for water, but of hearing the
words of the Lord:
12 And they shall wander from sea
to sea, &amp; from the north even to the
east, they shall run to and fro to seek
the word of the Lord, and shall not find it.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>GOD. REVEALING. HIMSELF. TO. HIS. PEOPLE
E-46 All right, you're the patient, aren't you,
sister? All right. First, before I take a hold of
your hand I want to talk to you just a little bit.
Cause you're just a little nervous, kinda upset
like. I want to get you in the right attitude of God,
mentally speaking, towards God's promise before
I pray for you.
Now, you believe Jesus is here? You believe these
things that I've said is the truth? They are? All right.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>Philippians 4
8 Finally, brethren, whatsoever things are true,
whatsoever things are honest, whatsoever
things are just, whatsoever things are pure,
whatsoever things are lovely, whatsoever
things are of good report; if there be any
virtue, and if there be any praise, think on
these things.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v13">
      <lines>Philippians 4
9 Those things, which ye have both learned,
and received, and heard, and seen in me,
do: and the God of peace shall be with you.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v14">
      <lines>LORD. I. BELIEVE
CHICAGO. IL
E-19 Now, Jesus Christ is here. Jesus Christ healed
the woman, and she can go home and be happy
now. See? Why? Just because you've come in
the right attitude. No one ever come to Christ in the
right attitude, but what went away with what they asked
for: no one. See?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v15">
      <lines>But you know in the eyes of Him Who shed
His Blood freely, I have a greater than that
before me tonight. For I have been given
the privilege to speak to the purchase of His
Blood.&quot;God so loved the world, that He gave
His only begotten Son, that whosoever believeth
in Him should not perish, but would have
Everlasting Life.&quot;</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
