<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Something In The Water</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v3 v7 v8 v9 v10 v11</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>He said, &quot;I've been where you've been before.
Down every hallway's a slamming door.&quot;
No way out, no one to come and save me
Wasting a life that the Good Lord gave me</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Then somebody said what I'm saying to you
Opened my eyes and told me the truth.&quot;
They said, &quot;Just a little faith, it'll all get better.&quot;
So I followed that preacher man down to the river</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>And now I'm changed
And now I'm stronger</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>There must've been something in the water
Oh, there must've been something in the water</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Well, I heard what he said and I went on my way
Didn't think about it for a couple of days
Then it hit me like a lightning late one night
I was all out of hope and all out of fight</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Couldn't fight back the tears so I fell on my knees
Saying, &quot;God, if you're there come and rescue me.&quot;
Felt love pouring down from above
Got washed in the water, washed in the blood</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>There must be something in the water
Oh, there must be something in the water</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>And now I'm singing along to amazing grace
Can't nobody wipe this smile off my face
Got joy in my heart, angels on my side
Thank God almighty, I saw the light
Gonna look ahead, no turning back
Live everyday, give it all that I have
Trust in someone bigger than me
Ever since the day that I believed</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>I am changed
And now I'm stronger</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>There must be something in the water
Oh, there must be something in the water
Oh, there must be something in the water
Oh, there must be something in the water</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>Oh, yeah I am changed
Stronger</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
