<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Stone by Stone</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v5</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Babylon, we know types the flesh Our worst enemy, who always,
Tries to get in the way When God wants to do something for us,
Jerusalem, we know types the soul, It is the soul that God contacts,
It is the city that God chose to dwell and identify Himself in</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>And though she's been mocked and scarred, laughed at,
Trodden down and buried deep under heaps of rubbish
God chose her and He loved her And we know that Jerusalem,
O, Jerusalem, Stone by stone, by stone, She shall rise and never fall again.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Babylon has fallen, Jerusalem shall rise,
God has promised he shall be built in perilous times,
This is the age God thought to place us in,
To fight the fight and to build the house
For our Jerusalem shall rise.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Some through the fire but those walls are rebuilding
With brotherly love those breaches are mending
We shall not cease until we hear that last trump sound
Until the capstone comes and crown the work of the Lord
Jerusalem shall rise.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Stone by stone, Jerusalem shall rise (x3)
From her filthy clothing, to her glorious white robe,
From the dust to the stars.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Jerusalem shall rise [Stone by stone, by stone, by stone]
We're putting down our Faith stone [Stone by stone…]
Our virtue and Knowledge stone [Stone by stone…]
Temperance and Patience stone [Stone by stone…]
Godliness and Brotherly kindness stone [Stone by stone…]
Our Chief stone and our Love stone [Stone by stone…]
Building a dwelling place for our God [Stone by stone…]
We're building our Jerusalem [Stone by stone…]</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
