<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>The Shaking</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v1 v3 v1 v4 v1</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Yet once more Lord, shake not just heaven but earth
And many stars are being moved out of place but
There were some who stood with Pleiades and Orion
In every age who kept their first estate
And though the powers of heaven are shaking
We’ve received the kingdom that cannot be moved
All that can be shaken it will be shaken.
Let thy word Lord, shake us into place</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>The heavens declare the glory of God,
Day unto day it uttered speech,
And Night unto night it showed knowledge,
For they are all in God’s perfect peak
For tell me what will happen
If the moon should leave her place,
Then the face of the earth will be a darken chaos again,
So what about the earthly host,
Who were made in the image of God,
If we are not in order how can we do the works of God?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>This world is again falling apart and soon
The millennium will be ushered in,
But first this kingdom, will be in you spiritually,
Before it comes in the earth literally,
But in the days of the ten toes
Came that rock cut without hands,
To smite every image in our earth made by man,
And know you not the kingdom
Of our Lord is in you,
For this stone did not only smite
But grew into a mountain too.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>We were like dry bones down in the valley,
Then the son of man came with a prophesy,
And out of his mouth came seven thundering voices,
To quicken and bring to life this scattered body,
Then came a noise and a shaking and each bone came to its bone,
Sinew, flesh and skin came upon on it but it had no life of its own,
No, but when he prophesied again, the dynamics came into that body,
So that we can be a mighty marching army</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
