<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>The Resurrection of the Bride</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v2 v4 v2 v5 v2 v6 v2</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>I’ve heard of Moses crossing The mighty red sea
And I’ve heard of Joshua leading
Israel to victory But in this day I’m looking for Present tense reality
I’m looking for the literal life of Christ To form in me</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>In the resurrection of the Bride
We can hear the thunders sounding
The pull is deep inside
And I am hearing Him call my name
So I’m looking for the quickening power
For the rapture and the change</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>We’ve heard of Jephthah and Gideon
Of David’s mighty men And we’ve heard of the power of Samson
When that spirit came on to him
So today we are looking for The third pull on display
When the mind of Christ is in the
Bride she’ll say</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>We know Bro. Willie and Wilson
Bro. Leon too
And Bro. John and Frankie Jacobs
Saints who stood tested tried and true
Sleeping saints and over comers
Victorious in this age
And in the better resurrection
They’ll be raised</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>This pull brought us out from Moab And from gleaning in the field
Where we met with the Lord of harvest
Whom His chief reaper has revealed
And now is the time of purging
We’re on that threshing floor
We’re being cleansed and sealed to sin no more
The token is what we’re longing for The end time Words come back to seed
The little Gentile Bride, she must conceive
For a blast of thunders and a prophet’s shout
Its full redemption will bring us out From the field of gleaning
Into God’s house</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Third pull power and authority
I want my body change And theophany
Oh yes, the sleeping saints will rise
And the Bride will take her flight
When the resurrection power is formed in me</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
