<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Till the Storm Passes By</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Out on the water, storms raging high
The waters around them, were troubled that night
Fear filled their hearts and they thought they would die
They failed to remember that the Master was nigh</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>He spoke the word, and the winds all stood s'til
Even the waters, they obeyed his will
And He calmed the storms, just like He will mine
If I'll just remember, that He lives deep inside</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>So why should I worry, and why should I fear?
The very same Jesus, He stays always near
He lives in my heart and He hears when I cry
I'll call on His name, 'til the storm passes by</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>We read in the bible, how He walked with them
Brought light to the darkness when the way grew so dim
How great it would be to have His steps leading mine
And to walk with the Master, all of the time</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>So when trials come, and death is so nigh
I just searched for the Master, He said He'll be there on time
Oh, and when I'm in trouble, and my body is in pain
All I have to do is call on His name</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>And why should I worry, and why should I fear?
When the very same Jesus, He stays always near
He lives in my heart and He hears when I cry
I'll call on His name, 'til the storm passes by</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Oh, and why should I worry, oh why should I fear?
When the very same Jesus, He stays always near
He lives in my heart and He hears when I cry
I'll call on His name, 'til the storm passes by</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>I'll call on His name
'Til the storm passes by
'Til the storm passes by</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
