<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Tree Song</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author type="words">David Mallett</author>
      <author type="music">David Mallett</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v5 v8</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>I saw a tree by the riverside one day as I walked along,
Straight as an arrow,
And pointing to the sky, growing tall and strong.
How do you grow so straight and tall?&quot; I said to the riverside tree.
This is the song my tree friend sang to me.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>I have roots growing down to the water.
I have leaves reaching up to the sunshine.
And, the fruit that I bear is the sign of the life in me.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>I am shade from the hot summer sundown.
I am nests for the birds of the heaven.
I'm becoming what the maker of trees
Has blessed me to be: a strong, young, tree.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>I saw a tree in the wintertime, when show lay on the ground.
Straight as an arrow and pointing to the
Sky and the winter winds blew all around.&quot;
How do you grow so straight and tall?&quot; I said to my wintertime tree.
This is the song that my tree friend sang to me:</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>I've got roots growing down to the water.
I've got leaves growing up to the sunshine.
And, the fruit that I bear is a sign of the life in me.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>I am shade from the hot summer sundown.
I am nests for the birds of the heavens.
I'm becoming what the maker of trees
Has meant me to be: a strong young tree.&quot;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>I saw a tree in the city streets where buildings blocked the sun.
Green and lovely, I could see it gave joy to everyone.
How do you grow in the city streets?&quot; I said to my downtown tree.
This is the song that my tree friend sang to me:</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>I am shade from the hot summer sundown.
I am nests for the birds of the heavens.
I'm becoming what The Maker of Trees
Has meant me to be: a strong, young, tree.&quot;</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
