<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>When I Take My Vacation</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Unbekannt</author>
    </authors>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v3 v5 v3 v6 v3 v7 v3 v8 v3 v9 v3 v10 v3</verseOrder>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Here so many are taking vacation,
To the mountains, the lakes or the sea;
Where they rest from their cares and their worries,
What a wonderful time that must be.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>But it seems not my lot to be like them,
I must toil thru the heat and the cold,
Seeking out the lost sheep in the mountains,
Bringing wanderers back to the fold.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>When I take my vacation in heaven,
What a wonderful time that will be;
Hearing concerts by the heavenly Chorus,
And the face of my Savior I'll see;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Sitting down by the banks of the river;
'Neath the shade of the ever green tree,
I shall rest from my burdens forever,
Won't you spend your vacation with me?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Now some day I shall take my vacation
To the city John tells us about;
With its foundation walls all so precious,
Where from gladness of heart I shall shout!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>O, no sights ever witnessed by mortals
Can compare with the glories up there.
I shall spend my vacation with Jesus,
On the place He went on to prepare.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>There the weather will always be perfect.
Not a cloud shall sweep over the sky;
And no earthquakes or cyclones shall threaten.
In the land of the &quot;Sweet by and by&quot;;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Soon there's going to be an excursion,
I am booked for a ride in the air,
You're invited to share my vacation,
And the feast with our Bridegroom to share.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>Here on earth when we take our vacation,
We return to our homes by and by;
When I take my vacation in heaven,
In those mansions of gold in the sky;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>I shall dwell with my Savior forever
With Him sit on His Heavenly throne;
All the days will be one, long vacation,
When my Savior takes me to His home.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
